Jack wants to marry Ben's mother. But there are strings attached.
Man of the House is a comedy, family film directed by James Orr.
Ben Archer is not happy.
His mother, Sandy, has just met a man, and it
looks like things are pretty serious.
Driven by a fear of abandonment, Ben tries anything and everything
to ruin the "love bubble" which surrounds his mom.
However, after Ben and Jack's experiences in the
Indian Guides, the two become much closer.
Jack Sturgess, played by Chevy Chase.
Sandy Archer, played by Farrah Fawcett-Majors.
Ben Archer, played by Jonathan Taylor Thomas.
Chet Bronski, played by George Wendt.
Lloyd Small, played by David Shiner.
Red Sweeney, played by Art LaFleur.
Man of the House is a 1995 American comedy film starring Chevy Chase, Farrah Fawcett,
Jonathan Taylor Thomas (in his debut film appearance) and George Wendt.
The film is about a boy (Thomas) who must come to terms with his potential stepfather (Chase), a well-meaning
lawyer who is unknowingly the subject of a manhunt by relatives of a man he helped land in prison.
It was shot in Los Angeles, California and Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada.
The tone is lighthearted.